记录日期 7-15-2
翻译
零九/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
记录日期 7-1-5-2
Log date 7-1-5-2.
我不敢相信我刚才做了那个
I can't believe I just did that.
我违反了我要遵守的命令并且违背了黄钻石的愿望
I disobeyed my orders and went against yellow diamond's wishes.
我是个叛徒草包！
I'm a traitorous clod!
我永远不想再回想起我所做的事情！
I never want to think about what I've done again!
我是个叛徒草包！
I'm a traitorous clod!
我永远不想再回想起我所做的事情！
I never want to think about what I've done again!
而且我称黄钻石是个草包，
And I called yellow diamond a clod,
当面的啊！
right to her face!
而且我称黄钻石是个草包，
I called yellow diamond a clod
当面的啊！
right to her face.
呃，橄榄石，你还好吗？
Uh, Peridot, are you gonna be okay?
我是个叛徒草包！
I'm a traitorous clod.
叛徒草包！
Traitorous clod.
不
No.
这一切都会好转的，你现在跟我们一队了！
It's all gonna work out. You're with us now!
你不明白
You don't understand.
我现在在保护之前试图摧毁的星球
I'm protecting a planet I was once trying to destroy.
我原本遵守每条指令-每个规则
I used to follow every order -- every rule.
现在我是个叛徒了
Now I'm a traitor.
一个反叛军！
A rebel!
一个水晶战士士士士士
A Crystal Gem-m-m-m-m.
草包！草包！
Clod! Clod!
看来，这个磁带录音机真是有用啊
Well, that tape recorder seems to be helping.
不，并没有！
No, it's not!
这是对我堕向癫狂的记录！
It's a chronicle of my descent into madness!
你丢了这个
You dropped this.
将它从我身边拿走
Get it away from me.
把它给史蒂文
Give it to Steven.
将癫狂退回源头！
Return madness to its source!
你确定你不想要吗？
Are you sure you don't want it?
无所谓，那是你的了，你的
Whatever. It's yours now. Yours.
不是我的，不是我的，你的，你的
Not mine. Not mine. Yours. Yours.
冷静一下
Let's calm down.
好吧
Okay.
那么，我是不是得在身上弄个星星？
So, am I gonna have to wear a star?
我要把星星放在哪？
Where am I gonna put the star?
她们看来关系不错嘛
They seem to be getting along well.
我很好奇是什么时候开始的
I wonder when that happened.
记录日期 7-1-1-2
Log date 7-1-1-2.
史蒂文给了我这个地球机器
The Steven has given me this earth machine
用来取代我的通讯器日志
to replace my communicator log.
它看起来...
It looks...
极度原始
Extremely primitive.
他还告诉我他希望我不要再称呼她“那个史蒂文”
He also said he wanted me to stop calling him "the Steven."
只用叫“史蒂文”
It's just "Steven."
我说我爱怎么叫就怎么叫！
I said I'd call him whatever I want!
他告诉我这很无礼
He told me that was rude.
无礼
Rude.
我想我以后会叫他“史蒂文”
I guess I'll call him "Steven."
地球的有机生命有非常奇妙的特点
The organic life forms of earth have fascinating traits
即使它们选了个非常糟的栖息地
despite their poor choice of residence.
我好奇它们是不是都有飞行能力？
I wonder if all of them have flight capabilities?
哦，你一定是橄榄石了
Oh, you must be Peridot.
喔！
Whoa!!
啊啊啊啊！
Aaaaaah!
橄榄石！
Peridot!
你想怎样？
What do you want?
你不能随便就将某个人从屋顶推下去！
You can't just shove someone off of a roof!
为什么不呢？
Why not?
这是个人类！
This is a human!
他不像我们！
He isn't like us!
他非常脆弱，而且柔软！
He's fragile and soft!
嘿，六块腹肌可不一定能在这个高度拯救你
Hey, it's not like a six pack is gonna save you from that height.
你本可能严重的伤害他
You could have seriously hurt him.
那么，我怎么能知道呢？
Well, how was I supposed to know that?
嗯
Hm.
格雷格，你得原谅橄榄石
Greg, you'll have to excuse Peridot.
她远离她的家乡，
She's far from her homeworld,
而且她仍在学习地球的一切
and she still has a lot to learn about our planet.
不，我才不是呢！
No, I don't!
对，你就是！
Yes, you do!
呃，嘿，对啊，别担心！
Uh, hey, yeah. Don't worry about it!
呃啊！
Ugh!
总而言之，
In conclusion,
不是所有的有机生物都能够飞行
not all of the organic beings here can fly.
另外，毋庸置疑的是，
Additionally, it is, without question,
永融体，石榴，是最差劲的
that the permafusion, Garnet, is the worst.
今天，我被分配了一项“杂务”-打扫工作-
Today, I was assigned a "chore" -- cleaning duty --
海绵宝宝你来错片场了吧？
好像我是珍珠一样
like I'm the Pearl.
这些土鳖不知道他们能有我是多么幸运的一件事
These clumps don't know how lucky they are to have me.
不过，在完成“杂务”时，
Although, while doing "chore",
我碰巧看到了一个箱子，其中有很多...
i did happen upon a container containing many...
衬衫
Shirts.
想象一下-外观挂件
Imagine -- appearance modifiers
还不是与你的身体连在一起的那种
that aren't melded to your body.
喔！
Oooh!
短裤很漂亮嘛
Nice shorts.
啊！
Aah!
这-这是怎么穿上我的？
How -- how did these get here?
啊啊！
Aah!
记录日期 7-1-1-2
Log date 7-1-2-2.
今天标志着我被捕后的第三十次地球自转
Today marks the 30th earth rotation since my capture.
满月被捕纪念日快乐！
Happy one month can-aversary!
圆柱体？
Cylinders?
这是高跷
They're stilts.
你将它们绑在脚上，它们则能让你变高
You tie them on your feet, and they make you taller.
我试着改进了一下外观
I tried to spruce them up a bit.
我不知道火焰有什么妖法，
I don't know what it is about flames,
但那的确让所有东西都更帅了
but they just make everything cooler.
你为什么要给我这些？
Why are you giving me these?
因为我希望你高兴一些
Because I want you to feel nice.
这就是礼物的作用
That's what gifts are for.
你给你的朋友们以表示你的关切
You give them to your friends to show you care.
然后他们会说，“喔，谢谢你！”
And they go, "wow, thanks!"
好像我愿意屈尊
As if I'd stoop so low
将你的地球垃圾绑在我身上一样
as to tie your earth trash to my body.
快给我滚！滚滚滚滚...滚！
Leave me! Go, go, go, go...go!
并且，喔，谢谢！
And, wow, thanks!
为何，没错，珍珠，我确实变高了
Why, yes, Pearl, I did get taller.
你的发现没错
How correct of you to notice.
当然，紫晶，我会给你取得
Of course, Amethyst, I will acquire
那些在非常高的架子上的芝士薯片的
those cheesy chaps for you off that very high shelf.
呀！喔
Hyah! Whoa.
倒着走也能用啊！
They even function in reverse!
“笑话”
"Jokes."
如何让
你周围的人
笑出声
而不是冷场
笑话！
“为什么鸡要过马路？”
"Why did the chicken cross the road?"
这是个经典的冷笑话
“因为鸡要到马路对面去”
"The chicken wanted to get to the other side of the road."
鸡是什么？
What's a chicken?
看起来地球人总是喜欢
It seems the earth ones are constantly
用毫无意义的娱乐品填充生活中的空虚
filling the voids of their life with meaningless distractions.
此处“Production Present”的logo与Pink Floyd的专辑“The Dark Side of the Moon”类似，
同时与Mabel梅宝的毛衣logo相像
“营地连心”前情提要...
On the last episode of "camp pining hearts"...
《营地连心》致敬《波西·杰克逊》系列，拥有相同的露营设定与主人公；
而《营地连心》的CP分布与《波西·杰克逊》相似
我不在乎你是不是在黄队，珀西
I don't care that you're on the yellow team, Percy.
我们能做到的！
We can make this work!
这可是“严色”战争，波莱特
It's coolor war, Paulette.
这对你毫无意义吗？
Doesn't that mean anything to you?
这是个什么奇怪的仪式？
What is this strange ritual?
呃，那是，呃...
Uh, that's umm...
他们是要试图融合吗？
Are they attempting fusion?
不，其实，我爸爸告诉我
No, well, my dad told me
在你生命中的某些阶段-
during certain stages in your life--
怎么会有人看这个放松自我，全是毫无根据的一派胡言！
how could anyone indulge in this, baseless drivel!
我可不愿意参合！
I'll have no part of it!
看“营地连心”的第78个小时
Hour 78 of "camp pining hearts".
第一次看《宇宙小子》的我
这可是“严色”战争，波莱特
It's the coolor war, Paulette.
这对你毫无意义吗？
Doesn't that mean anything to you? Doesn't that mean anything to you?
呃，你在这里已经好几天了
Uh, you've been here for a few days.
一切还好吗？
Is everything okay?
我一直在看
I've just been watching
你预先录制的娱乐内容
your previously recorded entertainment.
这是三天前的那一集吗？
Is that the same episode from three days ago?
难道不止一集？
There's more than one?
呃...
Mmm...
算了
Nah.
哦
Oh.
你画了个图
You made a picture.
图？这可不只是一张图，史蒂文！
Picture? This isn't just a picture, Steven!
这是个复杂的表格
It's a complex chart
一个分析
将露营者相互之间向荣的个性进行了分类
cataloging the compatible characteristics between campers.
不知为何被NTR的宿营草包没能认识到
Somehow the rejects at camp clod fail to recognize
皮埃尔和珀西这对CP的优越性
the superior pair that is Pierre and Percy.
其实，这是因为波莱特喜欢着珀西
Well, that's 'cause Paulette likes Percy.
波莱特，哈！
Paulette. Ha!
波莱特在营地的等级系统中毫无地位可言
Paulette has no place in the camp's hierarchy.
而皮埃尔-皮埃尔真是禽兽啊！
Now Pierre -- Pierre is a brute!
皮埃尔完全称霸了两人三足项目
Pierre laid waste to the three-legged races.
皮埃尔和珀西代表了最强的战斗组合
Pierre and Percy present the strongest battle formation.
他们完全主宰了整个营地！
They'd destroy the camp!
站CP的我
你从一集里提取了这么多信息？
You got all this from one episode?
这叫潜台词，史蒂文
It's subtext, Steven.
论《宇宙小子》狂热粉的分析能力
容我解释一下
Allow me to explain.
其实，首先，珀西和皮尔斯都属于黄队，而且-
Well, first of all, Percy & Pierre are both on the yellow team, and als--
我记得的这段
I remember this part.
珀西在用他的弹簧单高跷挽救她
Percy is using his pogo stick to save her.
更不用提珀西是个水上运动的老手
Not to mention Percy is adept at aquatic sports.
他本可以赢得独木舟比赛，如果他不是忙于追求波莱特的话，
He would have won the canoe race if he weren't so busy drooling over Paulette,
而且在珀西深入湖底取得
and the other part where Percy goes to the bottom of the lake
波莱特的友谊手镯的部分证明
to get Paulette's friendship bracelet proves that
他有整个营地最大的肺活量！
he has the largest lung capacity in the entire camp!
而皮尔斯是陆上最强力量，
And Pierre is a force to be reckoned with on land,
当他将铺位七的内衣挂在树上时，整个-
when he hung bunk seven's underwear in the tree, the whole--
而这正是为什么珀西和皮尔斯
And that's why Percy and Pierre
从客观上来讲最适合彼此！
are objectively the best for each other!
啊！
Gah!
记录日期 7-1-3-2
Log date 7-1-3-2.
融合簇的进展非常顺利，着令人意外
Progress on the cluster drill is going optimal, surprisingly.
虽然心怀怨言，明显有的职业道道-
Though I have a few complaints on the work ethic of --
嘿！
hey!
紫晶，干嘛
Amethyst, really.
现在不是四处瞎搞的时机
This is no time to be fooling around.
啊，别呀，小珍
Aw, come on, p.
我只是试图“狮解”压力
I'm just trying to Lion the mood.
“狮解”压力
Lion the mood.
你一直这么使用你的变形能力吗？
Do you always use shape-shifting like this?
你是指用来变酷吗？
You mean to be really cool?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
但这真是是...
But it's such a...
相对产出来讲极大的能量浪费！
Significant use of energy compared to the output.
那是什么？
What was that?
我一直在练习我的“橄榄语法”
I've been practicing my Perry-phrasing.
我感觉还不错，
Pretty impressive in my opinion,
不过仍然很难匹敌本尊
but it's hard to beat the original.
那么，你能变成任何东西吗？
So, can you shift into anything?
当然
Sure.
有要求吗？
Got a request?
呱！呱！我是只鸡！
Bok bok! I'm a chicken!
我摸清笑点了！
I get the joke now!
哈！对吧，至少她不再四处“狮解”了
Ha! Yes, well, at least she isn't Lion around anymore.
珍珠由于某些原因真的非常努力，
Pearl really tries for some reason,
而我也非常欣赏这点
and I can appreciate that.
紫晶的陪伴也非常有趣
Amethyst's company is entertaining, as well.
但，融合的那个
But, the fused one...
...困扰着我
...eludes me.
好吧，我们可以伴随进度追加人手，
Okay, we can add more support as we go,
但现在，我们只用抬起它然后将它放在顶上
but for now, we just have to pick it up and put it on top.
毫不费力
No sweat.
干吧！
Let's do this!
你的想法不错
You've got the right idea,
但我们也许希望更谨慎一点
but we might want to be a bit more careful.
收到
Gotcha.
来吗？
Shall we?
呃？啊！
Huh? Aah!
那看起来不错，我们休息一下
That looks great. Let's take a break.
什么？
What?
好吧，我受够了！
All right, I'm at my limit!
晚上好，橄榄石！
Evening, Peridot.
向我解释一下，融合体
Explain it to me, fusion.
我至少可以理解你的存在，
I can at least make sense of your existence
如果是为了功能性
if it's for a functional purpose.
但是你呢？
But you?
你并没有用你综合的尺寸与力量优势
You're not using your combined size and strength
做任何事！
to do anything!
我在做事啊
I'm doing something.
那是什么？
And what's that?
观星
Stargazing.
恶！你们可以独自做啊
Ich. You can do that alone.
我不想
Don't want to.
嗯...
Hm.
你可以从这里看到母世界所处的星系
You can see home world's galaxy from here.
你没错
You're right.
我们非常不同，我欣赏这点
We're very different. I appreciate that.
真的？
Really?
如果你真的想理解融合，我可以帮你
If you really want to understand fusion, I can help you.
你是指？
What do you mean?
我们融合吧
Let's fuse.
哦，我的星星啊！
Oh, my stars!
我明白，你还没准备好，这没什么
I get it, you're not ready. That's fair.
下次再说呗
Another time then.
不！
No!
不不不
No-no-no.
请-请等一下！
Just -- just gimme a sec!
准备好
Get ready.
啊！不不不不不！
Aah! No, no, no, no, no!
我做不到
I can't do it.
这没什么
That's fine.
橄榄石，我为你感到骄傲
Peridot, I'm proud of you.
为什么？！
Why?!
因为你愿意付出努力理解我
Because you've made an effort to understand me.
但我仍然不理解你啊！
But I still don't understand you!
为什么你们总是融合在一起呢？
Why are you fused all the time?
我是珀西和皮尔斯
I'm Percy and Pierre.
哦！
Oh!
好吧，上
Okay, go.
记录日期 7-14-2-
Log date 7-14-2 --
不，你要这么说，“7-1-4-2”
No, you say it "7, 1, 4, 2".
呃，记录日期 7-1-4-2
Ugh, log date 7, 1, 4, 2.
我尝试了与融合体石榴进行融合
I have attempted a fusion with the fusion Garnet.
我原希望由此获得对融合体更深入的理解
I had hoped to gain a better understanding of fusion.
不过我更深入了理解了石榴
Instead I gained a better understanding of Garnet.
等等，让它多录一会
Wait, keep it on a moment.
史蒂文，你可能在听本不该听的橄榄石的日志，
Steven, you probably shouldn't have listened to Peridot's logs,
但我知道你的好奇心源自对她的关切
but I know your curiosity comes from a place of caring.
你现在应该将录音机还给她了
You should give the recorder back to her now.
她会想要留下它的
She's going to want to keep it.
等等，什么？
Wait, what?
给你，橄榄石，将它拿回去吧
Here, Peridot, take this back.
我，谢谢
Wow. Thanks.